Okay. Okay. So to reiterate what I was saying, I think this is just, it's so
needed in this
industry, isn't it? Just to allow people to come and have a space to talk about
this stuff.
It's part of the beauty of this group, isn't it? There's lovely communities
that we can be
authentic and that we can have these hard conversations and that we can lift
each other up in these
conversations as well. And, you know, Georgia and I put a lot of time into
planning some of these
calls, but for this one, I was just saying to Georgia beforehand that I felt
like we kind of
wanted to just stay authentic and leave it as a bit of an open space for us all
to talk. And,
you know, Georgia and I have both got some ideas and things that we can talk
about. But also,
we'd love for you to have the space to talk about your own stuff, you know. And
that's part
of the conversation. The part of the conversation is coming away from
perfection and coming away
from feeling like we have to have it all worked out. You know, Georgia and I,
of course, we talk
about how we want things to be great, but we're just, you know, imperfect
people as much as anybody
else. So we're coming with our own ideas, but everyone will have ideas. And
hopefully, we can
just learn by supporting each other and being together in this space. So
with that said, I said to Georgia that it might be nice that if we started this
call by sharing a
little bit about our own journeys and about ourselves, because I think it's
easier to share
when somebody else has shared this, isn't it? So I hadn't had anything. I hadn
't had anything.
I just speak off the cuff. But for me, Kamen has been a huge part of my journey
. It's been
a huge part of my empowerment journey. So when I started Kamen, when I found
Kamen, I was about
five years ago now, wasn't it? And I just slipped up from my husband, who had
been in a very unhappy
marriage for quite a long time, about seven, eight years. I had two kids on my
own. And I was working
a job that I hated. I was managing a restaurant and studying and doing
placement. I was really
overworked, a bit overweight. I felt really crap about myself. Never, I hadn't
gone out or done
anything for a long time being married. And so Kamen was something for me that
opened up a new
well for me that made me feel like a woman, I suppose, for the first time for a
long time,
chatting to guys and realising that people were interested in me and there was
something I was
good at. And then I started buying loads more lingerie and started feeling
better about myself,
started getting fit and training. And it kind of spiraled, I suppose it kick-
started a news
a new stage in my life where I was focusing on myself. I was, you know, using
this
platform and this big sort of thing to focus on myself with the help of
beautiful people like
Georgia of course. And I really think that that's what it can do if we have a
supportive community,
because if you're doing it on your own and you get people leaving your room or
you get those quiet
days, you know, and it's knocking your confidence. It's really hard, isn't it?
But when we're here
together and we're all having these experiences, we all have good and bad days
and we're all
sharing our imperfections. And yeah, I think that can really help by sharing
our own vulnerabilities.
Georgia, do you want to share a bit about your kind of journey?
Hi everyone. So my life self-worth journey, I also didn't plan what to say
today. I was
going to, I had a little sporty and never afford to be best to just see what
comes out on the day,
because that would be most authentic, like I said. So my life self-worth
journey,
so it's been like, it's been a wild one really. Like, I felt like my whole life
since I was younger,
a lot of my world was focused on what I look like. Like, that was my fault, of
course, for example,
because I started modelling when I was 18, I started webcam when I was 18. I
didn't have
a community like this, so I didn't really have anyone around me. I didn't
really have an empowered
woman around me at that time. The women around me were very empowered, women me
were quite insecure,
but I didn't really, I was myself, like, massively massively massively insecure
,
and obviously with my jobs being about my looks, and then when I didn't get the
jobs or different
girls got photoshoots over me or webcam that wasn't going well, I sort of went
into a downward
spiral as well, because even in school, like, I was never the girl, like, the
boys wanted to date.
I do support me all these terrible names and call me flat chests and stuff like
that,
and I think that's part of the reason why I got a good job, although I do like
to say,
I got it from my shelf, I'm thinking about it now, I am hallowed them, and they
offer myself,
but back then, maybe there were comments, maybe do this kind of stuff, and tend
to surgery, and
extensions, big time, nails, makeup, eyelashes, all the rest of it, I've done
all of that,
and I was truly unhappy with myself, and it was all because I was so, so
insecure, and I was trying
to fix the outside, but it was obviously, as we all know, it's only the inside
that you need to heal
to feel great overall, so just moving away from Liverpool, and moving away from
people
hours around, and that really helped me on my journey to self-love, because I
think being in,
I think being in that environment wasn't good for me, because once again, it
was focused on a
lot of damage, and it wasn't very, for me anyway, but that's not what it's like
for everyone there,
or everyone, you know, within different parts of the world or whatever, but
just my circle,
which really focused on an emergent of 30 feet, and me coming away from that,
finally,
except for myself, myself, I took off all the makeup here, eyelashes, makeup,
weakness, obviously,
I didn't take these out, but I took everything else away, and just stripped
back on myself,
and I just worked on myself, like, from the inside out, like, what person do I
want to be,
like, I want to be, like, the most best friend for everyone, and like, just the
nicest person
anyone could need, that's what I want for myself, and that's what made me truly
love myself, because
it might sound big-headed, but I believe that I am, because I really, really
try my best to be,
like, to just be a nice person, and be good to people, and just do everything
from love, like,
I just do everything from love, and I'm probably rambling now, not making much
sense, because I
don't articulate myself very well, especially when I'm a bit nervous, and I
always have my
musicals, to be honest, but yeah, I think just doing things from a place of
love is what made
me truly love myself, because how could you not love yourself if you're
constantly just
given love, and trying to see love in every situation, and don't get me wrong,
I'm not paid
back, and I'm not always that way, of course, things do get to me, and I do
probably acting ways
that I shouldn't at times, but I can really try my best to just come back to
love, and that's
why I help me with myself, with Janey, and thanks, too, that's so nice, and
that, you know, it's
the reason why, you know, we are imperfect, and it's lovely to share, and you
know, if we're sharing
something from a script, it's not from the heart, is it, and you know, this is
what this is about,
sharing vulnerabilities as women, and part of what you were saying there, like,
about insecurity
and stuff, I think so many girls look at you, and you see just how beautiful
you are inside, but also
the outside as well, you know, there's no mistake in you are, like, incredibly
beautiful, and feel
that you maybe don't have those insecurities, or I've not felt that way before,
and can't connect
with you on that level, but it's important to share, isn't it, that we all have
those times,
we all have insecurities, and sometimes the people you see in the media who are
the most,
you know, who look the most beautiful, like the very vision of beautiful, may
have the most
insecurities, you know, because they're not looking at the other stuff so much.
Does anyone, does anyone else want to open up a little bit, does anyone else
want to share
their sort of either their content, or are they thinking about it right now,
there's no
precious move, if anyone wants to share something? Yeah, sure, I'll share.
Hello, hello, hello.
Um, yeah, I was bullied a lot in school, actually, from, like, um, age 6 to 16,
so 10 years, I was
bullied so much, and I always felt from, like, age 16 that I needed to show off
my, my looks,
because I, I was the ugly duckling and I turned into a swan, and so I always
felt everywhere
where I went, that I needed to be the most beautiful girl, everything was about
my looks,
I hated other women, um, I despised them, I was always trying to sort of, yeah,
I was, I was only,
only caring about my looks, I, I had no sisterhood at all, and I didn't even
know how to have
fun with my friends in a club or something, I was only busy with 30 with guys,
that was my
self-worth, it was very sad, actually, and then I went into this depression
where I didn't know
why I was anymore, I didn't know the little girl was anymore, that knew how to
have fun,
and not, not our level, like a deeper level, you know, so the past three years,
I've been, like,
super busy connecting to myself again, and finding out who am I truly, and
before that I also went
on, like, a lot of journeys, I traveled the whole world, I went to a lot of
spiritual teachers,
but the last three years have been, like, for me, and yeah, I've found true
sisterhood now,
especially here on Copenhagen with Georgia, and I'm also so happy with you guys
, you know,
it feels so warm to be so connected and feel so supported in this new job for
me that I
got since end of December, and I just love it, I feel like I'm tapping into
another part of myself,
yeah, more, I feel more empowered, I feel more radiant, and yeah, so grateful,
for finding you guys, actually, so beautiful, beautiful, so never doubt
yourself, thank you so much.
Thank you so much for sharing, Yala, that was so lovely, that was so nice to
hear.
And I've seen it too, like, obviously I'm Yala's friend over here in in
Thailand, and I've seen,
like, since you've started on the webcam, like, you really have been shining
even more, and it's
been nice because I know you've got yourself, like, in out of, out of
situations, and yeah,
you really like doing good by yourself by doing this, so it's nice to see.
Yeah, we're going to cry, thank you.
Oh, thank you, Yala. Does anyone else want to share how they're feeling at the
moment?
It doesn't have to be, you know, positive, you can share anything that's
worrying you, or
anything that's coming up for you, whether it's related to calm or self-worth.
Yeah, and you just think that you go through, obviously, being probably the
oldest,
and then you do go through different journeys at different powers in your life
as well,
and I was a bit like, when I was younger, I went a lot back and out of the
pictures,
and got, you know, I worried and I looked like that, you know, and then he saw
to get married,
I'd have kids, and he'd go through all his phases, and then I thought a few
years ago,
I thought it was about great, confident, I'd stand up in a room doing a talk
for three or four hundred people.
Now, obviously, with the hormones and all the rest of it going on, I've gone
through where I felt
like a shadow of myself, and all this overthinking and worrying, and it's like
messaging case,
he said, I'm going on, I know through my judgment, there's a little cross at
the top,
just quickly, if you don't want to do it. So, and then obviously, I was already
starting,
my husband took it off, he's getting through that, and then I obviously needed
to have experience,
but, you know, I think the way I'm going to try and view it, stop overthinking,
you know, go on as an actress, that's you, if they don't like you, that's the
end of it,
get rude, you know, but look after yourself, I mean, I've got into a lot of my
last sort of
five or six months of self-care, meditation, EFT, just trying to go out, I mean
, I can't walk
very about them, but we went out to a little village nearby, just got the gre
enery, but it does,
just for half an hour, you know, but I think things, you go through periods in
your life,
there'll be different things, you know, and even when you're doing well, there
's different stresses,
isn't there, you know, different things, but this self-care is so important,
even when you do,
you know, people are doing well, but for me, at the moment, it's, yeah, I find
to me, because
it's like an age thing, overthinking, which I would never have thought really,
but it's just,
you know, just life and hormones and situations, and I think because you want
things to work,
everything, I overthink, you know, go to the end of something where it's
probably going to happen,
you know, but I think that's it as well, and on this type of thing, you think,
or somebody will
like me or they'll be rooting, oh yeah, you know, just click the button and get
rid, so, you know,
I'm getting there with the overthinker than that, it's just, you have this
couple of major
setbacks, and that's it, isn't it, you know, well, it's such a lovely, lovely
group anyway,
with support and everything, so. Aw, thank you, thanks, Lauren and for sharing,
and yeah, you've
had a lot going on, haven't you since you started, so it's amazing that you're
still here, and it's
nice to hear people supporting you as well, like. No, no, I mean, I've planned
beforehand that this
is what I want to do, it's just unfortunate that things went a bit off, but it
might take an ill,
and then, you know, we'll dig in another book, no, no, I'm on track, and I will
get there, but
I've walked around and luckily I found you guys, that's great, but no, it is
definitely the way
for me, so thanks for your support, I do appreciate it. Aw, you're more than
welcome, and there's no
rush, is there, there's no rush, it's here where you need it, so that's good to
talk to yourself.
Um, does anybody else want to share? Anybody else want to share anything?
Um, I can say how cams helped me, but I've got a bit of a croaky voice, because
, um,
it was my son's 21st last weekend, and I just was in a tennis tournament as
well, and I've just
basically lost my voice, so, there we go. But yeah, um, I was just going to say
, I've always
escorted, um, for a lot of years now, and um, when COVID hit, obviously that
was something that
really affected me, and that's when I joined the ethical camera community, and
um, it was fantastic,
because I never even envisaged doing camp, or thinking that I could sort of end
a living from
that, and yeah, I proved to myself that I actually can, and thanks to that, um,
you know, I don't,
I can be much more like picky on who I see when I escort now, so it's much
nicer, so I thank you for
that. Aw, thank you, thank you for sharing that, and for being a part of this
as well.
Um, Cassie is just saying, she's almost crying here at work. Um, she just wants
to say, she's so
happy, um, that she started becoming a woman, she always wanted to be, because
of this group.
Aw, that is so nice, that is so nice, and Cassie, just to say, um, she had that
core,
because she won the competition with the Dominatrix, oh yeah, so I had a
message from the Dominatrix
yesterday, just saying how lovely work, Cassie, and how, um, she really
appreciated that time
with you, because it made her feel like she, she was helping, and you know, you
were so lovely, so
thank you as well. Um, so there was, I mean, I scribbled out a load of just
random notes,
which I thought, you know, certain things might be good to touch on today, and
I think that, um,
I think that one, one of the core things that's, that I want to touch on, that
I want to just talk
a little bit about is self-worth, and why, why, why is our self-worth the way
it is, why are we,
there are so many reasons, but working as a psychotherapist, you know, there
are core reasons why we feel
the way we do about ourselves, and, and I think that it really helps to
understand some of this stuff,
so that you can start to practise more of an inner focus. I think a lot of the
stuff we,
we meet myself and George just thought about talking about today is all about
inner focus,
so bringing your focus back to yourself. And, and I think that the first way to
do this is to
basically understand that, why, the reason why, why do, why do you feel this
way, why do we have
these feelings, why do we overthink? And it's because, trying to cut something
very long-winded
into very short and simple way of saying it, so our self-worth, we are of all
the mammals on this
planet, when we come into this world as babies, we are the most vulnerable, we
're really vulnerable,
we basically have three gestations, so there's three trimesters in a pregnancy,
but really there should be four, because the next three months when we come out
of the room,
when we're in the world, we're completely dependent on our caregiver,
completely dependent on the
people that are supposed to love us. So in that time, we learn that we are
completely dependent on
that other person, and this is when our brain is developing at such an
accelerated rate.
So we learn in that time that we have, in order to be pleased, in order to
survive, in order to
stay alive, we have to be able to communicate, we have to be able to please our
caregiver,
we have to be able to connect with them, and this shapes us so much, not only
in those first
three months, but for the first seven or eight years of our life. So we're
learning in that time,
how do I become acceptable as a person? How am I lovable? How do I get somebody
to look in my
face and how we well done? How do I get that? And so we learn from society, we
're given loads
of messages, especially as women, about who we should be, we should be pretty,
we should be
acceptable, we shouldn't be naughty, we should follow the rules, and so we're
getting all this
messaging, and we end up as an adult in the world, with all these thoughts, all
these self-critical
thoughts, and all these thoughts about who we should be, what we should be
doing, what's our life stage,
you know, and sort of, and we don't realise that actually we're adults now, we
're fully autonomous,
we no longer need somebody else to look after our needs, we no longer need to
be acceptable,
we only need to accept ourselves now. So freeing yourself at that, you know,
this thing that we
grow up with that innately, you know, we need it to survive, realising at some
point in your life
that this can now stop, I'm now autonomous, I now have control over my life,
and that doesn't
mean that you have to cut off with the people, or that you can't please other
people, but when
you bring your focus then, inwards to what you need, to what you want, to who
you really are,
away from trying to please other people, and you start to build yourself up
from the inside out,
and that really affects positively all your relationships, everything you do,
takes away so many barriers, and I guess you kind of start to find out who you
are, you know,
when you're free of all the cages that society has put you in for all this time
.
And so they, that's sort of the origins of self-worth, and we all have
different ones,
you know, we all grow up in different, you know, in the sameish society, but in
different families
who have different ideas of what it is to be a good person, whether that's
working hard,
or being attractive, or whatever else. So we all have those things, and I
suppose
there are simple ways, and there are complicated ways, there are lots of
different ways to bring
your focus back to yourself, bring your focus back to yourself. And even to
notice when your
focus is outward, so noticing when you're trying to please, noticing when you
're sat on cam,
and somebody doesn't want to have a conversation with you, and you're instantly
, oh my god, you
know, your focus is outwards on what the other person wants you to be, not on
yourself who you
or who you know you already are. So Georgia, I feel like I've rabbled on there
for a while,
do you want to talk about some of their like simple, nice things you were
saying to me about
how you sort of bring your attention back to yourself, like practical little
things that you do?
Yeah, and okay, well while you were in on that subject of like why the client
doesn't want to
talk to you, and then you know you get all flustered about that, I'll just
elaborate on that a little
bit more. Yeah, and because I was speaking to one of our like one of the
members, and she was saying
that it makes you feel quite, you know, she doesn't like it when people leave,
and it makes you feel
insecure about herself and stuff like that, and that's definitely how I used to
feel as well,
and now I know that it's because like it could be any reason, and now it doesn
't bother me,
but I knew that it once did, and I'm sure that it probably does bother some of
the members in
a group and maybe even some of the ladies here today, so I just wanted to touch
on that because
the member in questions she was saying like oh you know maybe like because of
this, or maybe
it doesn't like me, or maybe this, maybe that, and it's like we can't speculate
why it is to
leave in, or why they're not wanting to talk to you, or whatever it is, because
even if it is,
because they don't like the look of yeah, which is one reason what it could be,
it could be that
the laptop died, the wife walked in, we ran out of credits, you know, if we
just want to approach
to everyone, it could be anything, but as well as women or as like well that
member, for example,
she just went to, oh my god what the hell is that, these are honestly these
insects in this house,
I'm still not over the insects over the end of being near the year now, sorry,
I'm back to what
I was saying, even if it is like they don't like the look of yeah, why should
that affect like how
you feel about yourself, because just because it's one person doesn't like the
look of yeah,
like you're not going to be everyone's cup of tea, you know what I mean, and
you might not even
like the look of them, but you might not even see them because they just come
in and out, and not
if they come on, and what does that matter, if you don't like the look of them,
and they don't
like the look of you, it doesn't take anything away from me, but if you, so I
think that one thing like
to try not to do is when you're on common people are leaving, or you're not
getting many calls,
or if they are they're going straight away and stuff like that, don't speculate
what it could
be, why they're leaving, because you're just you're just like really taught
yourself with all the
reasons, and it might not even be any of them, so yeah that was that, and yeah,
I was going to talk
about some like self-love exercises you can do to bring yourself back to
yourself, oh my god what's
going on, you know overnight like the sun's just set, and the amounts of bugs
are flying, and these
these are the oils that are like this huge, and they like they're really
erratic, and they
fly, and they fly and like hit the walls and stuff, but anyway sorry I'm gonna
try focus now because
okay, so some self-love exercises, this is a good testimony, and the first
thing that I actually
forgot about is one thing to me that I really like is wearing this crystal, so
this is a rose
fourth crystal, and rose quartz is usually like symbolised, symbolised as self-
love, and whether
you believe it or not, or whether it actually works or not, or whatever else,
if you believe it to be
true then it's true I feel, so I put it on myself, and I feel like when I'm
wearing this, I feel like
I'm feeling self-love like I love myself, I've got other crystals that I really
ground, and I'm
powerful, and when I wear them ones I feel grounded and powerful because I tell
myself that's how I
feel that day, you can also get interested in these type of things, you can
actually get
rose quartz yoni eggs as well, I bought yalasum actually, I don't know if she's
still there, but
I think I don't know if she's being used them or not, where you put them inside
your vagina,
and it's actually good for like, kegol exercises as well, so like it tightens
your pussy as well as,
and I feel like when I'm wearing it inside myself here, and then on my chest, I
feel like the self
love is just like radiating for me body, you know what I mean, and I don't know
if that sounds like
one bird jumbo, but that's one thing that I like to do, but anyway, what I was
actually going to
talk about, so there's two self-love exercises I wanted to share, the first one
is basically
standing in front of the mirror, I would suggest being naked, or we're doing
whatever you feel
more comfortable in, but if you feel it to be naked then be naked, get yourself
some like
coconut oil or moisturizer or something that you know you can really like
massage yourself with,
and just standing in front of your mirror, maybe put on a song and that makes
you feel sexy or
empowered or silly or fun or whatever it is you want to feel in that moment,
just set the right
vibe, maybe like some candles or some incense, just really get it like a, like
a really nice vibe
for yourself, like really nourish yourself, and just rub the coconut oil or
whatever it is all
over your body and just, just thank yourself, just thank your body for what it
's doing,
yeah, because, and look at how beautiful it is too and how incredible it is,
because one thing
that I used to do, I used to always tell myself, oh my bums rubbish, my bums so
small, it's crap,
because I'm obsessed with trying to grow a bigger, bigger bums, and I used to
sound myself, my
bums so small, it's so this, it's so that, I'm really full hate on it, and no
wonder it was never
growing or never, like never flourishing because I was putting so much hate to
hateful energy on it,
and now I tell myself all the time, I've got such a big juicy ass, it's amazing
if this is that,
just and honestly since then I actually feel like it's been growing and I've
not been doing
anything different, yeah, I've been training in the gym, but I'm always
training in the gym,
and I don't know whether it's because it is, or whether I'm just looking at it
differently,
what it works for me, so that's something that I do as part of my coconut oil
ritual,
I always give my bum a bit of extra love, because it's something that I used to
really give a lot
of hate to, so yeah, just like, and not just how it looks or the outside, also
like our bodies are
keeping us alive, you know, we're able to, to walk and look after ourselves and
dance and play and,
you know, just breathe and whatever else stuff that we take for granted,
and so yeah, so that's one little exercise is just getting a fun step out and
just really just
massaging like oil over yourself, like how beautiful you're look and, and yeah,
just really tell yourself how amazing you are and how thankful you are for your
body.
And I think like, well, while you're doing that as well, just to add, I think,
you know, when you
look at yourself, you know, all of us probably, we look in the mirror and we're
like, oh god,
you know, you look to the part that you don't like the first, it's like to
remind yourself that
you were born into this life as love, you were born as love, you were born as a
baby who deserved
to be loved and cherished, and you've got to this point where you look in a
mirror and you,
you're judging yourself based on what you've been told about yourself is okay,
you don't own that,
somebody else gave that to you, so give it back, you know, you, you own love,
that's what you came
into this world as, and so these little judgments and snippets and things, when
you start to notice
that you're doing it, actively say to yourself, I'm giving that back, I'm
giving it back, I'm giving
that back, I'm reflecting it, you know, and so don't, don't, don't let it seep
into your consciousness,
don't take it in, notice you're doing it and give it back, you know, and it's
not even like you need
to claim something, like people think to become empowered, I need to get
something, I need to get
somewhere, I need to do this, this, and that, you already are, you just need to
give back the
stuff that you don't need, and what everything you need is already there, you
know, it's already there.
Yeah, definitely, thank you for adding that, that's a really good point to add.
So you haven't been making ass, George.
Thank you, I'm starting to feel that now like I'm starting to catch myself and
they're like,
yeah, like that looks good, and I used to really like, especially last year
when I was
away in America, I felt like I lost so much weight and I just felt like really
scrawny looking,
and I used to tell myself that every single day, like, oh, you're just so sc
rawny, and I'm like,
why would you do that to yourself, why would I put myself down like that, you
know what I mean?
And then I wasn't eating because I felt ill about myself and I just was in a m
oor down with spite,
also yeah, that's a thing of the past, now I've got a nice juicy ass, I think
sometimes I feel like
that way. So yes, okay, next exercise is this is what I actually learned to
have some girls
on this island, I was on a course, I think you've actually spoke about this on
your Instagram,
well, maybe about like, hugging yourself. So I was on this course, this course
where I learned
to like, dance with fire, and she started off by having us like, connect with
ourselves,
and one thing she had us do was give ourselves a hug, and at first, if they
feel really weird,
I'm not gonna lie, and I was just like, oh my God, what is she making us do
here? But honestly,
it was the best, it was a nice thing, and she told us to basically just hold
ourselves like,
you want to be held, and how you would hold a loved one, your child, your
partner, your mum,
or your friends, like, just really hold yourself with so much love. And maybe
we should all try it now,
because I think it's a nice exercise to do. So let's just give ourselves a big
hug, and just
really just get comfy in yourself, and just squeeze yourself, and just tell
yourself,
like, I've got myself, you know what I mean? I've got myself no matter what. It
might be silly,
but just do it, and the longer you do it, the more you'll feel good about it.
I was listening to something the other day, a podcast, might have been
yesterday, as well,
about sort of somatic practices in counseling, and one sort of good thing that
this does as well is
to remind you of the boundary of your body, like, your skin is your boundary,
everything that is
you as underneath, there is a boundary between the world and you, you know, so
while you're like
hugging yourself, you can think that all the stuff is inside, you're protecting
yourself,
and that's your boundary, that's your first boundary. That's true. But yeah, we
'll just spend
like another moment with ourselves. I like doing this one, and I think the more
you do it, the more
that you like, the more enjoyment you get out of it, because the more you feel
it, like you let go of
shame, and you know, anything, or any thoughts, you just let go of all that,
and you start to just
feel the moment. But yeah, they were my little exercises for self-love. Does
anyone have any
that they'd like to share, that they like to do? To give back to themselves? No
? No? Are you trying
to do that? I don't know. Sophie, hello. Let me think if there is one that I do
in particular,
which is another one that's really powerful, is to get a mirror, or handheld
mirror, for instance,
and just sit really relaxed and look into your own eyes, and put a Joe Cocker
with you are so
beautiful, on repeat. That's one is very like, you won't keep it dry. I am
telling you,
like, that's so powerful as well, because we used to, or used to looking in
someone else's eyes,
and tell them they're beautiful, or partner, or whatever. And if you look into
your own eyes,
you see that's purity, like when you were a baby, you know, you see that again,
and if you didn't hear
the words, you are so beautiful. I think we can't hear that enough.
Yeah, that's one that I like to give to my clients when I do life coaching.
Yeah.
I'm not trying that one, I'm too young. Sophie, did you want to share something
?
Yeah, I'm missing in a way, and it's kind of lovely here, and all this
empowering stuff,
and, but, literally, I think that I'm ready. I've literally just been standing
in the mirror,
rubbing my body with oil, so, yeah, I haven't been pregnant at all. And I
thought before that,
I would be like insecure about getting fat and whatever, but I'm fat, I'm
pregnant, and I feel
amazing. I'm growing into this human, and it's quite empowering, and obviously,
my time
is starting to change, but the guys are loving it, and I just didn't think it
would be like this, and,
but yeah, so, I mean, I'm a boyfriend with my body, and we're still like having
loads of fat, and,
oh, he's so, and yeah, just loving life, so it's good, I'm still terrified,
obviously, but,
yeah, it's just lovely listening to everyone, really. Thanks.
Thank you, Sophie, that's so nice to hear, that's so nice to hear.
Yeah, it is, thank you.
And, and I think...
Oh, sorry, you cut out a little bit there, oh, bye, you're going back to work.
Yeah, I should go to work if you're still listening. Yeah, okay. I should check
what time around,
I've got a lot of time left. And I think, like, one thing that I always, I
always come back to on
these calls anyway, and just in life in general, is like, about prioritising
your own pleasure as well.
Like, to me, that is the first way and the easiest way to show self-love,
because it can be as big as
like going on a big shopping spree, or going to a spa, or, you know, any of
those things,
or getting a treatment, or as small as like making yourself a nice coffee in
the morning,
you know, just appreciating a few things about yourself, you know, putting on
in the morning,
something that you like to put on, like, I wear nice lingerie every day, you
know,
even though I don't see my boyfriend most days, I do it for myself, because I
like to feel sexy.
And so yeah, prioritising your pleasure, thinking about even just little ways,
one little way, one or two little ways each day, that you can feel some
pleasure,
for no other reason than to just feel pleasure. And masturbation is a good one
as well, isn't it?
Self-pleasure. I really, I realised when we were talking, people talking on the
group
the other day, that not many people had toys, and the people that did have toys
, were talking about
the toys that they use with their partner, or they're even talking about their
partners thinking
what their partner thought about them having toys. And I think I forget that,
yeah, there is a
lot of judgment there as well as women that we, that we shouldn't have self-ple
asure in that way,
that it's not okay for us to have dildos, or ones, or whatever we want to self-
pleasure.
And I think that's an important part of self-love is like sexual self-pleasure.
And so coming back to that, I think it's good as well.
Yeah, definitely. I think like how you feel after you've had like an amazing
orgasm,
there's just no better feeling, you know what I mean? So why not give that to
yourself whenever
you can, or whenever you want to? Yeah, and it's also stress relief, I think.
Like in the day,
if I'm finding that I'm really stressed, and I need to like release something,
I might go for a walk,
or whatever, or I might just go upstairs and have an orgasm. And perhaps it
works.
And we connected to yourself.
And I suppose the last sort of the other points that I made that I was thinking
about talking about
was just about, so we talked a lot about ourselves, how we feel about ourselves
, what we can do,
how we can reconnect. But then there's also the other side, isn't that of like,
our insecurities are sort of insecurities on cam, like, and how we are affected
by other people.
I know we talked about like, you know, there's a million reasons why someone
might come out of
your room that have nothing to do with you, of course. But also, you know,
making room for
imperfection. One of my counseling supervisors said this to me once, because I
used to be very,
I used to get quite stressed about all my clients. I used to feel that I had to
have it all planned
out. I like to see progress quite quickly. So I'd feel a lot of pressure. And
he just said this
one sentence to me, and I just, but it stuck with me ever since. And he just
said, make room for
imperfection. And I thought, yeah, I do, I need to make room for imperfection,
because that is
reality. And, and I, and I feel that way about cam as well, that none of us
have it all worked out,
even if we're doing really well, we don't, we can't cater to every client, none
of us can, you know.
And I can try and draw someone into like my thing as much as I want, but if it
's not their thing,
it's just not going to happen. And so I think it's important to make room for
imperfection when you're on cam and not feel like you need to have it all
figured out before you
go on, and not to feel like you need to be dressed up to the lines or, and all
that stuff as well,
like looking the way you deem perfect to go on, because that's not helpful is
it. That puts a
lot of pressure on as well. Yeah, yeah, definitely that's something I also
wanted to touch on as well.
And because in the past, I used to like really pressure on how I looked on cam.
And recently,
well, when I say recently, the past couple of years, I've really just relaxed
it a lot more.
And on Sunday, for example, I had one of the best days I've had in, in years,
probably. And I
was completely natural on cam, like hair and makeup and even the outfit was
just a bikini. It wasn't
anything special. But it's because that day, I just felt like super confident
in myself. I felt
like I knew I was going to do good. I just, I just felt really good. And it
just mostly translated.
I didn't look anything like spectacular than like I ever did before or whatever
else, you know.
And so yeah, just don't put too much pressure on yourself on how you're looking
or what you're
saying. Because I found with a lot of my new stars as well, they're really like
, what do we say? And
what if they say something this and what if that? And it's like, I feel like we
're putting too much
pressure ourselves on trying to be like the perfect, the perfect cam girl,
which doesn't exist. But
yeah, just just relax and just be, and just like settle into yourself and how
you want to feel in
that moment. And I think that it'll just translate on cam if you're just
feeling powerful and stronger.
And like, yeah, I've got this rather than, but what if me here's out of place?
Or what if I say
the wrong thing or whatever else? Because let's be honest that you could be
saying all the right
things, what you think are the right things. And still it's the, it's for the
wrong client or for
someone who doesn't like those things to be said, you know what I mean? So yes.
Yeah. And one,
another thing I was thinking while I was talking as well, it was about how, you
know, sometimes we're
triggered into a story that is just not about what's happening right now. So
barely in mind,
this is fantasy. This is where someone has come to escape reality. So it's not
real. So someone might
come and, you know, say something and you think, Oh, guys always say that thing
to me. Like, why
do they feel they can say that thing to me? You know, you're then triggered
into your own story,
you're living your own thing. They don't even know what you're living in that
moment. They might
have a completely different idea about what they're doing. You know, they might
be a guy who works
at a checkout and all these colleagues hate him. And he's got no friends and he
gets, you know,
abuse at home. And so the one time where he feels free to feel like a man, he's
coming on Cam. And
then, you know, there's a whole of the story between each and every client that
we don't know about.
And so when we're checking into our own story about what, how it makes us feel,
it's good to just
remember that this is a playground, you know, this is a playground. It's
fantasy. It's not real.
And if we're triggered into something, it's probably because we've got some
work to do, you know, this.
And it might be as a result of like abuse or bad things we've suffered, which
are not our fault.
It's never our fault. But, you know, if we're triggered into something
consistently, then it
means that we have some work to do, you know, there's something there that is
that we're carrying,
which is good to do some work on, you know, in therapy or with friends or just
exploring it
yourself so that you don't keep being triggered by the same things.
Because that can easily happen, Khanit, when you're on cam, you can easily be
triggered by the same
words or the same attitude or whatever. Whereas, you know, it's something that
we're holding that,
and it's good to be able to let go of that stuff.
Yeah, definitely. Yeah, I like what you said then about it, like being a
playground, because
you know, all fantasy, because it really is like, it's not real, like not a
good real. It's just
people like chatting to your online and you get in these things called credits
and it ends up being
money and whatever else is just like, just try and look at this time, like,
look at it like this,
like this playground and it's like, you're separate from it, if you know what I
mean, like,
don't take it too personally, like if these say things that you don't like or
they're leaving or
whatever else, that's got nothing to do with you. That's on them. They want to
leave because they
want to leave for whatever reason or they said that because of what's going on
in their life.
It's literally got nothing to do with you. You know what I mean? So yes.
Yeah, you're a character in their story, basically. So, you know, it's up to
you how much you inhabit
that character, whether you take on the stress or whatever else on that
character, or if you just
be playful with it. And I think like when you said about it being a playground,
I kind of see like
life like that. I kind of feel like I'm playing with life. You know, I choose
what I want to play
with and what I don't, you know. And that's the beauty, isn't it, that we have
the power to do
that when we separate ourselves from it. Yeah, definitely. She knows to go, but
she's really
enjoyed it. And just going back to what you're saying there as well. It's also,
I think you get
caught up in comparing yourself, don't you, with other people and things. It's
like the whole face
book and Instagram thing. You see all these wonderful lives and then you might
just happen
to know somebody knows nothing like that at all. It's just the like portraying
a character and
actress or an actor. And you know, this is what they want, but they haven't
really got it, you know,
so we just get caught up in a small walk there, which I had that. Yeah, exactly
, exactly. And
that's why I think it's good for us to share our vulnerabilities because, you
know, I try and do
it on social media. I do try and post about things that struggle or bad days or
whatever. But, you
know, I never really post the proper ugly selfies, of course. So there is an
image there that probably
isn't reality. And it's good to talk about that stuff, isn't it? Yeah, I was
just typing back to
Eevee, sorry, I don't know if my type and affect things. But yeah, and use the
right, like, people
put like the best things on Instagram, of course. And I was speaking to someone
yesterday about this.
And even if the photo is not edited, which I think 99% of the time it is, even
if it's not,
it's still like a perfectly posed photo, best dangle, and then like two seconds
later, you could
take another photo of them. And it might look like a completely different
person, you know what I mean?
So you can't compare yourself to a photo that's been edited. You've got the
most like the perfect
outfit on heads, on makeup, on nails, on this that. And like, you know, like
the perfect still shot.
And then they're not actually that person anyway, you know what I mean? So yeah
, it's no good to
compare yourself to people on Instagram or Facebook or other work. And I do it
myself. And I try not
to. And I definitely need to do it like so much more than I do now. But it's
just like, it's just
losing it. You're just, you're just what it's supposed to say. You're just
fighting a losing battle
because you're never going to, it's never going to make you feel good. It's
just going to keep making
you feel like shit. It's just the worst thing you could do is to compare
yourself to people on
Instagram, which is the fakest thing I've ever seen. Like, yeah, it's
ridiculous. It's good to use
it like to utilize it as a tool. Like I use it for like, my Instagram was used
for my modern and
stuff like that. But I'm not even attached to the person I am on Instagram. It
's not even me. It's a
different, completely different person. That's just my, my like model persona.
If that makes sense,
and it's, it's a bit sad that people would compare themselves to people on
there, because it's just
not real at all. Yeah, but yeah. Yeah. And also, you know, remembering that,
like I was saying before,
like our insecurities were created, most of our insecurities were created, like
in a boardroom,
where the load of men, like, you know, they were created to make money from us,
to keep us feeling
insecure, to keep us feeling like this. So we're squabbling amongst each other
and comparing ourselves
rather than sitting in our power and actually reaching out for potential. So
when you think about it
like that, you can step back and be like, hang on a minute. I think this is a
bit too small for me
to be thinking about this. I've got better things that I can think, you know,
spend my time on myself,
you know. And yeah, yeah, that's something that I like to think about when I
find myself slipping
into comparing myself on like, okay, somebody, somebody, this was somebody's
plan that I would
do this. And I'm, I'm going to step out of that, I'm going to do that anymore.
Definitely. So we're coming to it's nearly the end of the hour. Um, does
anybody else want to
say anything? Is there anything anyone wants to share before we leave? I want
to, you know,
give you the opportunity to share anything? No. Okay. Well, um, I think we
should probably
mention about the competition as well. So the competition is like based on all
this stuff,
isn't it this month? Um, so it'd be really great if we could get some entries
to the competition,
maybe we'll post again in the group about what, what, what you need to do. So
there's different,
uh, sort of self-loved tasks to do. And we said that we'll donate to, um,
citizens of Ukraine for
every person that enters. So there's no prize this month. But I think that's a
nice enough prize,
isn't it, that you know, you're doing something good for other people. So, so
yeah, if you could
if you could enter, that would be amazing. Um, and yeah, I guess, I guess we'll
see you soon.
Yeah. And one more thing before we go ladies, I just wanted to, um,
just also remind us that we've got a call coming up on Monday, um, and it's all
about the text and
phone chat. Looking forward to that. Yeah. Yeah. And it's actually Sophia's
hosting a photo.
So thank you. We still heard us. Um, yeah, thank you for that Sophie. But a lot
of girls always
ask about it. And it's something that we've not really educated is on yet
because it's not
something that we've actually educated ourselves on. We've always just went as
a, we're a webcam
agency, but now we want to look into more. Thank you Sophie. We're looking to,
um, all the avenues
really. So I'm really grateful that, um, we're very grateful that Sophie's
going to do this for us.
And then after that, we'll be able to, um, really like educate you as more on
this kind of thing
than give you advice on it. So it's on Monday at half 12 UK times. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
So hope to see us all there or if not, no, it's what you're back. Oh, great.
Thanks for the call,
ladies. Thank you. Nice to see you. Bye. Bye everyone. Bye. Have a good day.